MANDA SHIVA REDDY

SALESFORCE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

9182912375

mshivareddy@gmail.com

SKILLS

Configurations - Workflows, process Builder, Flows Approval process, Record types, Security Model, Validations, Creating Profiles, Roles, Users, Page Layouts, Email templates, Reports & Dashboards.

Customization - Apex class, Apex trigger, Asynchronous Apex.

Lightning Component - Aura and Lightning Web Component (LWC).

EDUCATION

National Institute of Technology, Kurukshetra

2019-2021 (M. Tech) Aggregate 9.3 CGPA

Nalla Malla Reddy Engineering College

2015-2019 (B. Tech) Aggregate 80.1%

Pratibha Junior College

2013-2015 Aggregate 93.8%

CERTIFICATIONS

- Salesforce Associate
- Platform Developer I

PROFILE

To succeed in an environment of growth & excellence and earn a job which provides me job satisfaction and self-development which helps me to achieve personal as well as organizational goals. Have 1.5+ years of experience in IT industry. In-depth Understanding of Configuration and Customization in Salesforce.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesforce Developer | NoblQ Solutions

(Jeevan Technologies Acquired By NoblQ Solutions)

Chennai - April 2024 - Current

Salesforce Developer | Jeevan Technologies

Chennai - April 2023 - April 2024

Salesforce Intern | Dev Rabbit IT Solutions

Tirupati – Jan 2023 - April 2023

Online Data Analyst | TELUS International Al

Remote – March 2022 – Feb 2022

PROJECT

Agency Workspace

(April 2023 - Sep 2023)

Description:

The goal of the Agency Workspace is to keep track of customer insurance information. The project was developed by community cloud so that the agent, agency, or customer can log in and make an Enrollment for the client with a variety of policies through the Benefitmall website.

Responsibilities:

- Understanding the business requirements and developing Design and Solution Developed
- Involved in development of SFDC Application using Apex classes, Apex Trigger. Worked on Asynchronous Apex Class, Data loader, Test class.
- Creating and maintaining technical documentation, including design specifications, test plans and user guides.
- Performed unit testing for User stories and bug fixes.

Paradigm (Deloitte Project)

(Oct 2023 - Current)

Description:

• This application is developed in Salesforce platform to check Risk advisory for the entity globally. To verify the risk factor of the entity for various region. Paradigm cases play the major role in verifying the conflict and business relationship of the entity.

Responsibilities:

- Created Lightning Component and server-side controller to meet business Requirements.
- Created multiple Lightning Components, added CSS and Design Parameters that makes the Lightning Component look and feel better.
- Providing ongoing support and maintenance for Salesforce applications, including troubleshooting and resolving issues.
- Testing the developed components using test class for apex logics.
- Creating and maintaining technical documentation.